http://www.airblast.com/legal/privacy-statement

Airblast paint rooms
Graco plural component sprayers.
PRIVACY POLICY
Airblast B.V., situated in The Netherlands, Nijverheidsplein 2A, 1704 RB  Heerhugowaard is liable for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our services.Contact information Airblast B.V. Nijverheidsplein 2A 1704 RB  Heerhugowaard The Netherlands Tel.: +31 72 5718002info@airblast.comwww.airblast.com
Data collection and use We use your data to provide and improve our services. By using our services, you agree to the collection and use of personal data in accordance with this policy.
Personal data collected Airblast B.V. collects the following personal data: • First name and last name • Company name • Company address • Phone/Fax number • E-mail addressSpecial private data Our website and services do not knowingly collect special private data. If you believe we have collected special private data without your authorization, please contact us through info@airblast.com. We will remove that information from our records.Use of data Airblast B.V. uses the collected data for various purposes: • To send you our newsletter • To be able to contact you in order to provide and maintain our services • To notify you about changes to our products and services • Airblast B.V. also uses private data if legally required, such as information necessary for tax declarations. Automated decision making Airblast B.V. does not use profiling techniques or technology to automate decision making in conflict with privacy laws.
Retention of data Airblast B.V. will retain your personal data only for as long as necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.Disclosure of data Airblast B.V. does not sell your personal data to third parties and only discloses personal data to provide and maintain services to you. Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your personal data if legally required or in response to valid requests by public authorities. We may employ third party companies to facilitate our services. These third parties have access to your personal data only to perform these tasks on (y)our behalf and are held by contract to the same protection level of your personal data as set in this Privacy Policy. Airblast B.V. remains liable for this use of personal data.Cookies Airblast B.V. does not use cookies to track the activity on our website.Your rights You have the right to view, rectify or delete personal data we hold about you. You also have the right to request restriction to processing your data and to the withdrawal of your consent to processing your data. You can request to obtain a copy of your personal data in a commonly used format so that you can manage and move it (data portability).You can send your request in this matter to info@airblast.com. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests by asking you to send us a copy of your ID on which the following needs to be obscured: the picture, MRZ (Machine Readable Zone, the numbers at the bottom side of the ID), ID-number and personal identity number or social security number (BSN number). We will react swiftly on your request, at the latest within 4 weeks. If you feel Airblast B.V. does not comply to your wishes in line with GDPR, and is not able or willing to resolve the issues you encounter in that respect, you can file a complaint with theDutch Data Protection Authority. The contact details of the Dutch Data Protection Authority are obtainable through following link:https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/en/contact-dutch-dpa/contact-usSecurity of data The security of your data is important to us and we take appropriate measures to counter abuse, loss, unauthorized access and unwanted disclosure. If you feel your personal data is not well protected or if there are any signs of abuse, please contact us through info@airblast.com.
contact
Industries
shipyard
oil & gas
petrochemical
pipeline
metal
construction
Airblast B.V.
